Richard A. Jenson collection, Inclusive: 1982-1997, undated; Bulk: 1988-1992, undated
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Judicial, 1982-1994, undated; 3
  - State, Tom Phillips, Texas Supreme Court, Clippings (1 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - State, Tom Phillips, Texas Supreme Court, Clippings (2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - State, Mario Ramirez, 332nd District Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - State, C.L. Ray, Texas Supreme Court, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - State, C.L. Ray, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Party Manners, Fairly Honest, Susan Howard-1, Susan Howard-2, Spanish-1, Spanish-2”, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - State, Ted Robertson, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - State, Ted Robertson, Texas Supreme Court, Campaign Button, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - State, Ted Z. Robertson, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “English TV, Spanish TV”, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - State, Ted Z. Robertson, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “Robertson En Espanol”, undated (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - State, Ted Z. Robertson, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “The Trial”, 1988 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - State, Nelda Rodriguez, 13th Court of Appeals, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - State, Barbara Rosenberg, 5th District Court of Appeals, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - State, Homer Salina, 92nd District Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - State, Doug Sandage, 125th District Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - State, Mike Schless, 353rd District Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - State, Ross Sears, Texas Supreme Court, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - State, Robert Seerden, 13th Court of Appeals, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - State, Madeline Sitzes, 127th District Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - State, Bob Slagle, Texas Supreme Court, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - State, Carleton Spears, 150th District Court, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - State, Franklin Spears, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - State, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - State, Texas Supreme Court, VHS Tape, “’92 Supreme Court Justice Candidates Debate”, 1992 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - State, Texpac Supreme Court Clinic (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - State, Texpac Supreme Court Clinic (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - State, Hugo Touchy, 129th District Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - State, Norman Utter, 13th Court of Appeals, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - State, Bill Vance, 10th Court of Appeals, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - State, Art Vega, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - State, Art Vega, Texas Supreme Court, Campaign Button, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - State, James Wallace, Texas Supreme Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - State, David West, 269th District Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Local, Wilfred Aguilar, County Court No. 5, 1987, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Local, Robert G. Blum, Justice of the Peace, Potter County, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Local, Will Flowers, Travis County Court No. 6, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Local, Alberto Garcia, County Court No. 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Local, Don Harrison, Justice of the Peace, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Local, Roger Jones, County Attorney, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Local, Brenda Kennedy, County Court at Law No. 7, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Local, Carole Keeton Rylander, Mayor, Austin, VHS Tape, “Carole Keeton Rylander Political Ad”, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Local, Cleve Moten, County Court at Law No. 2, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Local, David Phillips, County Court at Law No. 1, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Local, Cliff Roberts, Justice of the Peace, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Local, Sylvia Robertson, 179th District Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Local, Richard Teniente, Justice of the Peace, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Legislative, 1984-1994, undated; 4
  Series IV. Legislative is organized by level of government: federal, state, and local. Within each level of government, folders are organized alphabetically by the candidate's last name.
  The federal section relates to races for the U.S. House of Representatives and U.S. Senate.
  The state section is the largest section of the series and consists of materials for Texas House and Texas Senate races. Temple Dickson and Chet Edwards are featured here.
  The local section relates to members of city councils or precinct commissioners with a specific focus on the city of Austin, Travis County, and Potter County.
  - Federal, Mike Andrews, U.S. House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Federal, Lloyd Bentsen, U.S. Senate, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Federal, Lloyd Bentsen, U.S. Senate, Campaign Button, 1988 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Federal, Phil Bredesen, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Federal, Tom Daschle, U.S. House of Representatives, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Federal, Lloyd Doggett, U.S. Senate, circa 1980s (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Federal, Bob Edgar, U.S. Senate, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Federal, Martin Frost, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Federal, Sylvia Garcia, U.S. House of Representatives, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Federal, Pete Geren, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Federal, Henry Gonzalez, U.S. House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Federal, Michael Herzik, U.S. House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Federal, Edward M. Kennedy, U.S. Senate, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Federal, Peter Kostmayer, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Federal, Sandy Kress, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Federal, Jim Lane, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Federal, Ed Lehman, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Federal, Gerald McCathern, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Federal, Thomas O’Neill, Jr., U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Federal, Hugh Parmer, U.S. Senate, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Federal, Jake Pickle, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Federal, George Richardson, U.S. House of Representatives, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Federal, Max Sandlin, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Federal, Bill Sarpalius, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Federal, David Skaggs, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Federal, [Lamar?] Smith, U.S. House of Representatives, Window Sign, 1987 (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Federal, Tom Vandergriff, U.S. House of Representatives, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Federal, Timothy Wirth, U.S. Senate, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Federal, Jim Wright, U.S. House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - State, Tommy Adkisson, Texas Senate, circa 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - State, John R. Anderson, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - State, Richard Anderson, Texas Senate, 1986, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - State, Kenneth Armbrister, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - State, Johnnie Lou Avery, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - State, Gonzalo Barrientos, Texas Senate, 1986-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - State, Hugo Berlanga, Texas House of Representatives, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - State, Mark Bragg, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - State, John Bryant, Texas House of Representatives, Campaign Pin, undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - State, Katy Caldwell, Texas House of Representatives, District 134, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - State, Jim Chapman, Texas Senate, 1987-1988, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - State, Melchor Chavez, 1994 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - State, Paul Colbert, Texas House of Representatives, 1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - State, Karyne Jones Conley, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - State, Anne Cooper, Texas House of Representatives, circa 1988 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - State, Debra Danburg, Texas House of Representatives, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - State, Wilhelmina Delco, Texas House of Representatives, District 50, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - State, Betty Denton, Texas House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - State, Temple Dickson, Texas Senate, circa 1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - State, Temple Dickson, Texas Senate, VHS Tape, “Income Tax Returns”, 1988 (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - State, Temple Dickson, Texas Senate, VHS Tape, “Temple Dickson Campaign”, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - State, Temple Dickson, Texas Senate, VHS Tape, “Experience”, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - State, Temple Dickson, Texas Senate, VHS Tape, “The Choice”, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - State, Temple Dickson, Texas Senate, VHS Tape, “Temple Dickson”, undated (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - State, Chet Edwards, Texas Senate, 1989, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - State, Charles Finnell, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - State, Maria Luisa Lulu Flores, Texas House of Representatives, District 51, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - State, Ted Lyon, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - State, Nef Garcia, Texas Senate, 26th District, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - State, Bob Glassow, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - State, Sherri Greenberg, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - State, Wayne Grisham, California Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - State, William “Billy” Hall, Jr., Texas House of Representatives, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - State, Jim James, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - State, Clay Jenkins, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - State, Eddie Bernice Johnson, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - State, Jack Jones, Texas House of Representatives, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - State, Robert Junell, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - State, Quentin Kopp, California Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - State, Libby Linebarger, Texas House of Representatives, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - State, Gregory Luna, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - State, Jennifer Mattingley, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - State, Oscar Mauzy, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - State, Glen Maxey, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - State, Ronald McCluskey, Texas House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - State, John McDonald, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - State, Mike McKinney, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - State, Bob Melton, Texas House of Representatives, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - State, Margaret Moore, Texas Senate, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - State, Elliott Naishtat, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - State, Juan Ochoa, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - State, Jesse Oliver, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - State, Ernest Perales, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - State, Mary Perkins, Texas Board of Education, undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - State, Mel Phillips, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - State, George Pierce & Alan Schoolcraft, Texas House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - State, Steve Portnoy, Texas House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - State, Scott Roberts, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - State, Paul Ruiz, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - State, Larry Don Shaw, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - State, Charles Soechting, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - State, Curtis Soileau, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - State, Dick Swift, Texas House of Representatives, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - State, Carlos Truan, Texas Senate, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - State, Jim Turner, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - State, Hector Uribe, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - State, John Whitmire, Texas Senate, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - State, John Whitmire & Ramon Martinez, Texas Senate, VHS Tape, “April 1991 Campaign John Whitmire/Ramon Martinez TV ads” (Box 11 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - State, Ralph Yarborough, Texas Senate, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - State, Cassette Tape, “73rd Committee of the whole Senate on Redistricting Ethics and Elections”, 1993 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Local, Tom Blackwell, County Commissioner, Travis County, undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Local, Craig Bryant, Precinct 1 County Commissioner, Travis County, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Local, Troy Burrus, Precinct 3 County Commissioner, Potter County, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Local, Smoot Carl-Mitchell, City Council, Austin, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Local, Barbara Climer, Precinct 3 County Commissioner, Potter County, undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Local, Harold L. Cliver, Precinct 1 County Commissioner, Potter County, undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Local, Bill Filante, Assemblyman, Marin and Sonoma Counties, California, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Local, Lowell Lebermann, Austin City Council, undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Local, Gilbert Martinez, City Council, undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Local, Michael “Max” Nofziger, City Council, Austin, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Local, Sally Shipman, City Council, Austin, undated (Box 5, Folder 75)